## Curriculum Vitae

#### Daniel Goble

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

danielgoble@gmail.com 07889 558 385 I have extensive experience within the creative design industry having worked across a broad range of projects within the fields of user experience and interaction design, user interface design, visual communication and graphic design.

Throughout my career I have applied these disciplines across web based products and services, native mobile apps, streaming media and television UI.

#### CAREER HISTORY

# Samsung Design Europe | Jan 2022 - Present Senior Product Designer

My current position within a research and development area of Samsung allows me to push and challenge the creative design aspects of my skillset, as part of a team responsible for identifying future facing trends and proposing cutting edge experiences for emerging technology and features across the full range of Samsung industry leading products and services.

# T3 Awards Best TV Platform

The Connies Winner Contribution to User Experience & Best TV / Video Launch

TV Connect Awards
Shortlisted for Best Cloud
Based Video Service &
People's Choice

Content Innovation Awards
Winner for Advanced TV
Innovation of the Year

## Warner Media | Nov 2019 - Dec 2021 Senior Product Designer

As a member of the International Design Team my responsibilities involved leading UI and UX design work for some of Warner Media's most populer customer facing brands such as Cartoon Network and TNT Sports and supporting involvement with the HBO Max streaming service.

Joining the team at an early stage in its evolution allowed me to play a key role in the development of the design systems and processes that were employed across the range of digital products.

#### Massive Interactive | May 2019 - Nov 2019 Senior Product Designer (contract)

My work here centred primarily on the ground-up product redesign for a major global sports streaming service. This involved liaising with a dedicated UX design team in order to apply updated brand elements and enhance existing design systems across mobile, tablet, web and TV. I was also involved in pitch work for other global brands such as Formula 1 racing and Cathay Pacific.

#### BT Innovation Awards Finalist for BT Touch

"Thank you for the wonderful Turner On-Line feature. I live in the US, and this is a fantastic way to share your collection with those of us unable to visit the gallery in person"

(Tate Online user)

### YouView TV | Jul 2015 - Apr 2019 Senior Product Designer

My primary role here involved helping to create and evolve an entirely new user interface for the YouView set top box, allowing users to enjoy a combination of live and on-demand television in a seamless and intuitive manner. Secondary to this, conceptual work on the YouView mobile app was also undertaken. Both projects involve an agile collaboration between UX, visual design and development teams, with projects going through cycles of concepting, prototyping and user testing.

### Tandem Bank | Jun 2015 - Jul 2015 Digital Designer

Joining this disruptive banking startup, my role involved hybrid UX/UI duties. Primary focus was placed on the conceptualisation and design, both UX and visual, for a series of financial services mobile apps aimed at simplifying common customer needs.

#### Blinkbox Music / WE7 | Nov 2012 - Jun 2015 User Experience & Interface Designer

Initially employed as a dedicated user experience designer for the Blinkbox music (formerly WE7) tailored music streaming service, my experience in UI design was latter brought into play as my role evolved into a hybrid UX/UI position.

As part of the UX team I was tasked with creating and enhancing a new online experience, helping to define how users interacted with the UI on both the web and the iOS and Android apps.

Work was carried out in an agile environment and involved a process of sketch sessions, low fidelity prototyping and user testing before any UI design work was then undertaken.

## British Telecom | Nov 2000 - Sep 2012 Junior Graphic Designer - Senior Creative Designer

My time at British Telecom is a significant part of my career. Joining as a junior graphic designer I spent these years honing my skills and experience within multiple different teams and working across a wide variety of projects, both customer facing and B2B.

Highlights from my time here include my work with the Tate Britain gallery, for whom I created the Interactive Turners Gallery - which was heavily covered by the media and still draws many visitors to the main Tate website. I was also involved in the London 2012 Olympics campaign, tasked with the creation of a range of online marketing material.

#### **CORE SKILLS & EXPERIENCE**

User experience and interaction design
User interface design
Creative graphic design
Visual design for native apps & responsive web
User centred design techniques and application
Prototyping (both low and high fidelity)
Motion design
Information architecture
Usability and basic accessibility principles

#### FORMAL TRAINING & EDUCATION

User Centred Design (Flow Interactive)
Inclusive Design (best practice)
HTML / CSS
Design for Print
Presentation Skills
Typography
Use of Colour

National Diploma in Media and Film City & Guilds in motion photography

#### SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

I am proficient with most industry standard design software. Some favourites include:

Sketch
Figma
Adobe XD
After Effects
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator